[{"answer": "As I've just said, I made the claims in the select committee.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "All right, Mrs. Mensch, do you want to respond to that?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Well, it was -- it was very dramatic.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "What was it like for you being so close to that?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Well, right after the attack took place, I started speaking to the police who were running around.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Jonathan, what do we know about the attacker?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "I think it -- miraculously, the pie may have saved the whole day for the Murdoch family.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "How did they do?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "No, I actually don't think I would agree on that.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Would you agree with that, that it's the pie what won it?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Clearly on the fundamental question which never got answered.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "And from what you saw, Richard, I mean, where would you say that the Murdochs were at their weakest today?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Have you had any reaction from the family since the end of the hearing today?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "I think it's quite a surprising position, and there is a difference between your reaction to this and I think that of most of the European public because most of us have never done business with Rupert Murdoch and know what he's like inside.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "I mean is that a position that is acceptable for a guy who's chairman and CEO of News Corporation?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Yes, I most certainly would.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Would you see it that way?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Oh, no, no, no, no.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "And finally, Richard, I mean greatest scandal in British history from your experience?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Well, I tell a lot of stories in my standup act that, you know, or my points of view of different things.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Well, I think if you do standup, the kind of standup I like, you've got to tell the truth and you know hopefully you've had some interesting things.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "To put it mildly, haven't you?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Well, I can't think of anything.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Is there anything about your life that you can't joke about?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "My battle with food and my weight is the core of every -- of my alcoholism, of everything.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Your weight, the way you look, everything?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "I need to lose some weight.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "And how are you feeling these days about the way you look?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "I remember working at Hormel very well.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Did you remember that experience well?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "I was.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Were you a good hog slayer?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "So -- yes, it was first --", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "ORGAN: What?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Well, me, Mike, and Mo, who are still buddies of mine to this day, there's nothing to do in Ottumwa, Iowa, after 10:00.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "You did what?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Terrifying.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "What was that moment like?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "The first time I got offered a paying job, $15, I was in University of Iowa and I had some standup.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "When was the moment that you realized this could be a career and not just a bit of fun for you?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "You know, but people have to understand, I haven't talked to her, you know, face to face in almost 18 years.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "I mean is that a good thing or not a good thing for you?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "I'd say good luck with your show.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "And what would you say to her if she's watching?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Part of her, no.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Do you think she'll be pleased that you're happy?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Rather impressive remarks there I think, Tom, don't feel your old friend Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Well, you have to understand he grew up in a -- much like me in a small town in -- in Austria in his case.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "What do you make of what's been going on?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Were you -- were you as shocked as everybody else?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Well, we see each other.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "About what's been going on?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Well, the only joke that I can crack is that he can no longer make fun of the women that I've been with.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "At what point can you crack a joke about this?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I think it's a go.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Is that a go, or is it -- but might it happen?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Absolutely we've been talking about it.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "You've been talking about it?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I think Arnold is a great man.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "The -- what kind of man is Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "It is torturous, and it's monotonous.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "I mean, it's like a -- it's a torturous process, isn't it?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "You've made 100 movies?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I loved \"True Lies\" --", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Which is your favorite?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "I think there was one.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "The one you don't like to talk about in civilized company?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I was about a half ounce a day --", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "-- at your worst, what are we talking in terms of consumption?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "-- of cocaine.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Well, I will tell you this.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Did you remember how that made you feel?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Do you -- do you drink at all now?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Literally nothing at all?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "I -- I watch people sometimes, normal people.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "And do you ever get tempted?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "I have regrets about the way I acted, you know, when I was using drugs and alcohol.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Did you have any regrets about it, or is it something that happened to you, that you're just pleased you moved on that was for a long time probably quite a bit fun?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Well, relationships wise, if your mom leaves when you're four, you know, anything is possible.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "How much of what went on then do you think determined how you became in your earlier adulthood?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "I just -- I just said what I had to say.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "What did you do?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Did you hit him?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "And did it bring you any kind of closure?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I love Charlie.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "When you see someone like Charlie going through what he's been through the last few months, what's been your -- your view watching from afar?", "qSentId": 757}, {"answer": "That's the immorality of -- of everywhere.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 785, "question": "I mean, there in a nutshell is the immorality of Hollywood, isn't it?", "qSentId": 784}, {"answer": "I -- there was a night.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 804, "question": "What in the end made you stop?", "qSentId": 803}, {"answer": "Well, if I'd have continued partying, obviously I wouldn't have anything.", "docId": "110719pmt", "aSentId": 869, "question": "Have you managed to, despite all the partying and the extravagances and so on, have you retained enough to be pretty comfortable the rest of your life?", "qSentId": 868}]